School of Computing Science fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committee files, 1972 - 1994; F-93-3; 85 cm of textual records
  - University - Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries (SCSAB) files, 1980 - 1984; F-93-3-42; 1 cm of textual records
    Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries
    - Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries (SCSAB), 1980 - 1984; F-93-3-42-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
  - University - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies (SCUS) on Computers files, 1982; F-93-3-43; 1 cm of textual records
    Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies
    - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies (SCUS), 1982; F-93-3-43-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
  - External - British Columbia Computers in Education Committee files, 1981 - 1986; F-93-3-44; 1 cm of textual records
    British Columbia Computers in Education Committee
    - British Columbia Computers in Education Committee, 1981 - 1986; F-93-3-44-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
  - External - Canadian Computer Science Department Chairmen Committee files, 1982 - 1987; F-93-3-45; 1 cm of textual records
    Canadian Computer Science Department Chairmen Committee
    - Canadian Computer Science Department Chairmen Committee, 1982 - 1987; F-93-3-45-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
- Director's correspondence files, 1972 - 1986; F-93-4; 29 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Chair's/Director's correspondence with school program areas and faculty, other university programs, and external (non-university) individuals and organizations. Activities, events and topics documented include technical reports, graduate and undergraduate curriculum development, Faculty Association meetings and case files, interdisciplinary program development with other faculties, SFU's Speaker's Bureau, Student Society, involvement with professional organizations, and Ted Sterling's cancer research.
  Records include correspondence, reports, notices, letters, budgets, proposals and working papers.
  This series was created by the archivist in July 2004 to provide structure to the creator's general subject files. Correspondence has been grouped into the following sub-series by type: Departmental, Faculty Association, University, External. Within each sub-series, files are arranged alphabetically.
  - Departmental correspondence - general, 1972 - 1980; F-93-4-1; 2 cm of textual records
    - Computing Science Program - educational use of computer time, 1973; F-93-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Computing Science Program - exchange on proposals, 1972; F-93-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Computing Science Program - technical reports, 1975 - 1976; F-93-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Graduate curriculum correspondence, 1980; F-93-4-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Undergraduate curriculum correspondence, 1980; F-93-4-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
  - Faculty Association correspondence, 1973 - 1975; F-93-4-2; 3 cm of textual records
    Simon Fraser University Faculty Association
    - Faculty Association - general, 1973 - 1975; F-93-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty Association - meetings, 1973 - 1975; F-93-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty Association - scales, 1973; F-93-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty Association - workload, 1975; F-93-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty Association - case file #1, 1974; F-93-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty Association - case file #2, 1974; F-93-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
  - University correspondence, 1972 - 1983; F-93-4-3; 13 cm of textual records
    - Academic - General Correspondence: Wilson, B.G. (Vice-President), 1973 - 1974; F-93-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Assistant Vice-President - Dr. Ian Mugridge, 1972 - 1973; F-93-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Engineering Program Correspondence, 1980; F-93-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty - status, 1981; F-93-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Arts - Department of Archaeology, 1973; F-93-4-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Arts - Department of Economics and Commerce, 1972 - 1979; F-93-4-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Arts - Department of Geography, 1972 - 1974; F-93-4-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Arts - Department of Political Science, 1972 - 1975; F-93-4-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Continuing Education - Dean, 1973 - 1976; F-93-4-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Education - Dean, 1973 - 1976; F-93-4-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Education - general, 1973 - 1975; F-93-4-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 93-10)
    - Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies - Communication Studies, 1973 - 1978; F-93-4-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies - Computing Science Program, 1974 - 1980; F-93-4-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies - Dean, 1972 - 1978; F-93-4-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies - Dean, 1981 - 1983; F-93-4-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies - Department of Kinesiology, 1973 - 1977; F-93-4-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Science - Department of Biological Science, 1972 - 1976; F-93-4-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Science - Department of Chemistry, 1973 - 1975; F-93-4-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Science - Dean, 1972 - 1974; F-93-4-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Science - Department of Mathematics, 1972 - 1978; F-93-4-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Faculty of Science - Department of Physics, 1973 - 1974; F-93-4-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Graduate Studies, 1972 - 1979; F-93-4-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Jewell, Ross - Chairman, Computing Centre, 1972 - 1973; F-93-4-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Lower, S.K. - Chemistry, 1974; F-93-4-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Memos to Dean Calvert, 1977; F-93-4-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - President of Simon Fraser University, 1974; F-93-4-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Reinstatement Issue [PSA Controversy], 1974; F-93-4-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Speaker's Bureau - Ken Mennell, 1973; F-93-4-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Student Society, 1974 - 1977; F-93-4-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - University News Service, 1974 - 1976; F-93-4-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Vice-President Academic, 1974 - 1978; F-93-4-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
  - External correspondence, 1972 - 1986; F-93-4-4; 10 cm of textual records
    - Association for Computing Machinery (ACM), 1976 - 1977; F-93-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Canadian Information Processing Society (CIPS), 1975 - 1977; F-93-4-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Computing High School Project - general correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-93-4-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Computing Science Chairmen, 1974 - 1976; F-93-4-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Data Processing Program for Paraplegics - John Krauss, D. Wilson project, 1973; F-93-4-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Douglas, Dr. Virginia, 1973 - 1974; F-93-4-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - High school computing course - correspondence to Wayne Dodds, 1973; F-93-4-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - IFIPS Committee on the Relationship between Computers and Society, 1976; F-93-4-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Institute of Chartered Accountants, 1974; F-93-4-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Science Day, 1986; F-93-4-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - Statistical Science Association of Canada, 1973 - 1975; F-93-4-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 93-11)
    - T. Sterling - cancer research continuation application CA10208-07, 1972; F-93-4-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
    - T. Sterling - cancer research correspondence to Washington University regarding grants, 1973; F-93-4-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
    - T. Sterling - cancer research final report, 1972; F-93-4-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
    - T. Sterling - review of papers, 1973 - 1976; F-93-4-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
- Project, research and grant files, 1981 - 1987; F-93-5; 10 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to grants, scholarships and awards prepared or received by faculty members during the course of university-wide, national and international research. Included are funding applications for Simon Fraser University President's Research Grant Stipend, Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC), Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council (SSHRC) and the Science Council of British Columbia. Noted research projects include the Canadian Society for Fifth Generation Research; proposal for a National Microelectronics Facility; a joint proposal by Computing Science, Engineering Science and the Physics Department; and planning for a site visit to SFU by NSERC.
  Records include grant application forms and policies, proposals, financial budgets, correspondence, reports, minutes, faculty curriculum vitae, working papers, statistics, contracts and agreements.
  - Canadian Society for Fifth Generation Research, 1983 - 1984; F-93-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
  - Grants, Scholarships and Awards, 1981 - 1982; F-93-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
  - Grants, Scholarships and Awards, 1983; F-93-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
  - Grants, Scholarships and Awards, 1984; F-93-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
    Restricted in whole
  - Grants, Scholarships and Awards, 1985; F-93-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-12)
  - Grants, Scholarships and Awards, 1986; F-93-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
  - Grants, Scholarships and Awards, 1987; F-93-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
  - Natural Sciences and Engineering Research Council (NSERC) visit, 1986; F-93-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
- Computing laboratory, centre and facility files, 1971 - 1989; F-93-6; 22 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the establishment and operation of computing laboratories and other facilities used by students and faculty for research and coursework completion. Activities, events and topics documented include the Centre for Systems Science (CSS), the Computer Graphic Centre, the Computing Centre, and the proposal for a remote academic terminal. Also included are records on the Computer Assisted Instruction Centre (CAI), Computing Science Instruction Lab (CSIL), and the Laboratory for Computing and Communications Research (LCCR).
  Records include correspondence, reports, course files, policies and proposals, and working papers.
  This series was created by the archivist in July 2004 to provide structure to the creator's general subject files. Records related to specific computing laboratories or facilities have been assigned a separate sub-series and files are arranged alphabetically.
  For further records on the Laboratory for Computer and Communications Reasearch (LCCR), see School of Communication fonds (F-92, sub-series 4-0-0-15).
  - General files, 1972 - 1989; F-93-6-1; 6 cm of textual records
    - Centre for Systems Science, 1988 - 1989; F-93-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Computer Graphic Centre, 1972 - 1973; F-93-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Computing Centre, 1973 - 1977; F-93-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Computing Centre - External Review, 1975; F-93-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Remote Academic Terminal, 1974; F-93-6-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Widjet, 1980; F-93-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
  - Computer Assisted Instruction Centre (CAI) files, 1971 - 1975; F-93-6-2; 9 cm of textual records
    - Computer Assisted Instruction Center (CAI) - administration, 1971 - 1972; F-93-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Computer Assisted Instruction Centre (CAI) - correspondence general, 1973 - 1975; F-93-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Computer Assisted Instruction Centre (CAI) - correspondence and reports, 1971 - 1973; F-93-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - Computer Assisted Instruction Centre (CAI) - facility reports, 1973; F-93-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-13)
    - CAI - Invitational Workshop in Interactive Computers in the Classroom, 1974; F-93-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
    - Report on Computer Assisted Instruction at SFU - material circulated, 1973; F-93-6-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
    - Computer Assisted Instruction Centre (CAI) - Tentative draft for final report, 1973; F-93-6-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
  - Computing Science Instruction Lab (CSIL) files, 1981 - 1986; F-93-6-3; 3 cm of textual records
    - Computing Science Instructional Lab (CSIL), 1981 - 1983; F-93-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
      Open, no restrictions
      Reviewed for access (Feb 7, 2024) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Computing Science Instructional Lab (CSIL), 1983 - 1986; F-93-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
  - Laboratory for Computing and Communications Research (LCCR) files, 1981 - 1985; F-93-6-4; 5 cm of textual records
    Laboratory for Computer and Communications Research
    - LCCR - correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1981 - 1983; F-93-6-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
    - LCCR - correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1981 - 1983; F-93-6-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
    - LCCR - correspondence and reports, 1983 - 1985; F-93-6-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-14)
      Restricted
      Reviewed for access (Feb 8, 2024) – File includes records that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (educational history, employment history, personal contact information). File restricted in whole, but may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
- Curriculum and instruction files, 1970 - 1991; F-93-7; 1.82 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to credit and non-credit instruction offered by the School and its predecessors. Activities, events and topics documented include the evaluation of courses, new course proposals, curriculum rationalization and scheduling, development of Continuing Education courses, cross-listed courses with other departments, Programs of Distinction, Programs of Excellence, seminar and colloquium series, high school computer course development, the Summer Computing Institute, workshops, and the graduate and undergraduate program.
  Records include correspondence, reports, course files, working papers, policies, lecture schedules and outlines, reading lists, student self-study guides and handbooks, assignments and essay questions, final exams, directed studies proposals and teaching evaluation summaries.
  Some teaching material has been retained (e.g. glossaries, lecture notes), but reprints of articles have not been preserved. The sub-series on "Course files" does not include course administrative records (e.g. enrollment lists, book requisition forms, grade change forms, registration status reports, waiting lists, add/drop forms, lab fee notices). Note that record types found in the files vary considerably from course to course.
  Series is arranged into sub-series that make a distinction between those files that relate to general curriculum planning and specific course files. The material has been arranged according to the original filing system of the creator. Course files are arranged chronologically by course number and year.
  For detailed information related to course descriptions and the graduate and undergraduate program, see the course guides, brochures and student handbooks found in "Publications" (series F-93-8).
  Some records contain personal information relating to students or faculty. Access to these files is restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Curriculum and instruction - general files, 1970 - 1988; F-93-7-1; 20 cm of textual records
    - Academic - evaluation of courses, 1973 - 1974; F-93-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Academic - courses 1974 PL/I seminar correspondence, F-93-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Automata Theory courses - R. Haroop: Mathematics, 1972; F-93-7-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Automata courses - memos, 1973 - 1975; F-93-7-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Battleship, [197-?]; F-93-7-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Computer Curriculum Study, 1970 - 1974; F-93-7-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Computer Education courses, 1980; F-93-7-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Computing Science Programme - master copy, 1972; F-93-7-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Computing Science - professional degree, 1974; F-93-7-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Computing Science in Education - teaching materials (Egan, Ellis, Sterling), 1973; F-93-7-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Continuing Education - courses given by Computing Science, 1973 - 1976; F-93-7-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Continuing Education - division of courses, 1973 - 1974; F-93-7-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Continuing Education - lecturer, 1974 - 1975; F-93-7-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Continuing Education - TV course, 1975; F-93-7-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Course proposal - Computing Problems in Chemistry, 1972; F-93-7-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Cross listing of courses in Math and Chemistry, 1973; F-93-7-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Digital Systems Design Honors Program, vol. 1, 1976 - 1981; F-93-7-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Digital Systems Design Honors Program, vol. 2, 1976 - 1981; F-93-7-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Fundamental Theory of Computation, [197-?]; F-93-7-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Graduate Program, 1974 - 1979; F-93-7-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - M.A. Program in Education - Computing Science emphasis (Draft), 1973; F-93-7-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Material for high school computer course - main folder, 1972 - 1973; F-93-7-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Management (Business) Information Systems, [197-?]; F-93-7-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Management Systems - CMPT 368 (Dr. Pollack's course), [197-?]; F-93-7-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Mathematics courses relative to Computing Science courses, 1973; F-93-7-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Mini computer course, 1972; F-93-7-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Practicum for students in Information Science and Educational background, [197-?]; F-93-7-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Programs of Distinction, 1981 - 1985; F-93-7-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 93-15)
    - Programs of Excellence, 1979; F-93-7-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Seminar and Colloquium Series, 1982 - 1986; F-93-7-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Special courses in Computers and Experimental Design, 1972; F-93-7-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Transfer of Computing Sciences courses from BC Regional Colleges, 1973 - 1974; F-93-7-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Undergraduate Computing Science Program, 1981 - 1985; F-93-7-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Undergraduate Computing Science Program - master copy of program report, 1972; F-93-7-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Undergraduate Computing Science Program - revised master copy, 1973; F-93-7-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Undergraduate Computing Science students, 1985 - 1987; F-93-7-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
    - Workshops, 1983 - 1988; F-93-7-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 93-16)
  - Course files, 1973 - 1991; F-93-7-2; 1.63 m of textual records
    - Introduction to Computers and Programming: An Experimental Course, 1973; F-93-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - Computing Science - grading policies, 1974; F-93-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - Special Arrangement - Geography and Computing Science Computer Mapping course, 1979; F-93-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - Summer Computing Institute (SCI), 1981; F-93-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - CMPT 001-3 Computers and the Activities of Man, 1974 - 1975; F-93-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - CMPT 001-3 Computers and the Activities of Man / People, 1976 - 1985; F-93-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - CMPT 001-3 Computers and the Activities of People, 1986 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - CMPT 100-3 Computing Science Introduction to Concepts and Procedures, 1974; F-93-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 93-17)
    - CMPT 100-3 Computing Science Introduction to Concepts and Procedures, 1975; F-93-7-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 93-18)
    - CMPT 100-3 Basic Programming and Software for Business Students, 1984 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 93-18)
    - CMPT 101-4 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1982 - 1984; F-93-7-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 93-18)
    - CMPT 101-4 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1985 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 93-18)
    - CMPT 102-3 Introduction to Programming for Science Students, 1974 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 93-18)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1974 - 1976; F-93-7-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 93-18)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1977; F-93-7-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 93-19)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1978; F-93-7-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 93-19)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1979; F-93-7-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 93-19)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1980 - 1981; F-93-7-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 93-19)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language I, 1982 - 1984; F-93-7-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 93-20)
    - CMPT 103-3 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language B, 1985 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 93-20)
    - CMPT 104-1 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language II, 1974 - 1978; F-93-7-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 93-20)
    - CMPT 104-1 Introduction to a High Level Programming Language II, 1979 - 1991; F-93-7-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 93-20)
    - CMPT 105-3 Introduction to Computing, 1975 - 1978; F-93-7-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 93-20)
    - CMPT 105-3 Introduction to Computing, 1979 - 1980; F-93-7-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 93-21)
    - CMPT 105-3 Introduction to Computing, 1981 - 1983; F-93-7-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 93-21)